In this exercise, you are asked to setup a Multi-AZ ElastiCache cluster.
在此练习中 将要求您设置多 AZ ElastiCache 集群
We can see that the first thing we should do is set up our Subnet Group.
我们可以看到 我们应该做的第一件事就是成立我们的子网小组
When we look at our subnet group,
当我们看到我们的子网群时
we can see that we have set up the group with multiple subnets,
我们可以看到我们已经建立了这个有多个子网的这个集团
which lead us to multiple availability zones.
将我们引向多个可用性区域
Once we have our subnet group created,
一旦我们创建了子网组
then we can create our cluster.
然后我们就可以创建集群了
We can see that once our cluster is created,
我们可以看到一旦我们的集群被创造
we have multiple nodes within the cluster.
集群中有多个节点
We can see their current role as either a primary or replica,
我们可以将他们的当前角色视为主要或副本
and we can also see that they are spread across multiple availability zones.
我们还可以看到它们分布在多个可用性区域中